İletişim Bilgileri

salihdemir5335@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/salih-demiir (LinkedIn) demirsalih.com.tr/ (Personal)

En Önemli Yetenekler

Microsoft Intune
Microsoft Entra ID
Active Directory

Languages

İngilizce (Full Professional)
Türkçe (Native or Bilingual)

Salih Demir

System & Network Specialist - Novartis

Ataşehir, İstanbul, Türkiye

Özet

I am here to start my career as a junior software engineer with a deep interest and passion for the software world. It is very important for me to gain experience by using the theoretical knowledge I gained during my education in real-world applications. As a dedicated junior programmer, I have a strong desire to follow technological innovations and improve myself accordingly. I enjoy working collaboratively but can also run projects independently. I also believe that my problem-solving ability and communication skills have motivated me to do more.

Deneyim

Novartis IT Specialist Ocak 2024 - Present (11 ay) İstanbul, Türkiye

Teknonet Bilgisayar Sistemleri Information Technology Help Desk Ağustos 2023 - Kasım 2023 (4 ay) İstanbul, Türkiye

Inditex Markalarına Zara,Bersha,Pull&Bear,Massimo Dutti,Zara Home,Lefties Tüm Türkiye mağazalarına destek vererek IT HelpDesk uzmanlığı pozisyonunda deneyim elde ettim.

Payten

Engineering Intern Mayıs 2023 - Temmuz 2023 (3 ay) İstanbul, Türkiye

Android Developer olarak Android takımındaki projelerde katkıda bulundum. MARVEL

Diversey
Information Technology Intern

Mayıs 2022 - Nisan 2023 (1 yıl)

Ataşehir, İstanbul, Türkiye

Ranna Digital Works React Native Developer Kasım 2021 - Ocak 2022 (3 ay) İstanbul, Türkiye

Casper Türkiye Stajyer Eylül 2016 - Haziran 2017 (10 ay) İstanbul, Türkiye

Eğitim

Doğuş Üniversitesi

3,00, Bilgisayar Yazılımı Mühendisliği · (2020 - Temmuz 2023)